（忆往昔）
我活在你脑袋里
I am inside you.
难道只有我感觉这就像个笼子吗
Is it me, or is this just like the cage?
梅格
Meg.
迪恩 可怜的卡西迪奥都死了
So, Dean, what's poor, dead Castiel doing.
怎么会出现在外面的那辆破车上
in that junker out there?
- 他不知道他是小卡 - 我知道
- He doesn't know he's Cass. - I know.
我们这么办吧 我需要盟友
So, here's the deal … I need friends.
我们直接去找萨姆
We go straight to Sam.
你是说没有别的法子了
So, you're saying there's nothing?
我不能让这个问题消失
This isn't a problem I can make disappear.
但我也许可以将它转移
But I may be able to shift it.
这不好吧 我们不能就这样丢下他
I don't know. I mean, we can't just leave him.
我们不能带着他
Well, we can't bring him with us.
这世界上的妖魔鬼怪都在找我们 这样安全
Everything on the planet's out for us, okay? This is safer.
欢迎加入我们 马斯特斯护士
Welcome to the team, Nurse Masters.
迪克在资助一个考古挖掘项目吗
So Dick's funding an archaeological dig?
太棒了
Outstanding.
你一拿到箱子就会给我电话吧
You will call as soon as the package is in hand.
不知道 但他很迫切想拿到它
I don't know. Whatever it is, he wants it bad,
那我们就要拿到它 没得说
which means we got to grab it, end of story.
我找这个已经找了很久很久了
I've been looking for this for a very, very long time.
- 现在怎么办 - 问得好
- So now what? - That's a good question.
我们先逃出几千里再想这个问题吧
Why don't we answer that a few thousand miles away from here, though?
（如今）
（美国中等学校国家学生社团认证会员 凯文·谭）
（密歇根州 内博市）
（伊利诺伊州 芝加哥南部）
（大提琴练习结束）
喂 凯文
Hey, Kevin.
普林斯顿大学刚把2013年录取率
Princeton just adjusted its acceptance rate.
- 降至8.7% - 深呼吸 凯文
- down to 8.7% for 2013. - Breathe, Kevin.
你在学习吗
Are you studying?
我正和你聊天呢
I'm talking to you.
我十四分钟后开始学概率论和统计
I'll start on probability and statistics in 14 minutes.
我痛恨概率论
I hate probability.
明天是我拿到完美数学成绩的最后机会
Tomorrow's my last chance to get a perfect math score.
你的SAT（相当于美国高考）很高啊
Your SATs are great!
钱宁 所有人的SAT都很高
Channing, everybody's SATs are great.
我得达到完美
I have to do perfect.
谁说的
Who knows?
申请文也很重要啊
The essays are at least as important.
（入学申请文）
我实在没什么可写的
I have absolutely nothing to say.
我懂 我懂你的意思
I know. I know what you mean.
我读过一个被康奈尔录取的学生的文章
I read one by a kid who got into Cornell.
他都没有胳膊和腿
He didn't have any arms or legs or anything.
整篇文章都是用嘴打的
He had to type the whole thing with his mouth.
写得很不错
It was beautiful.
我死定了
I am so screwed.
不管我们表现如何 有一天
You know, no matter what, one day,
上大学什么的都是浮云了
college isn't going to matter anymore.
你胡说什么呢
You're out of your mind.
就为块破石头这么兴师动众的
That's a lot of fuss over a caveman lego.
对啊
Yeah.
迪克要的东西就封在这里面
Well, whatever Dick wants is bricked up inside that.
好吧
All right.
这雷声像不像有人对你说「等等 住手」
That sound like somebody saying, "no, wait … stop" to you?
有点
Uh…yeah. Yeah.
是啊
Yeah.
不管了
Oh, well.
[邪恶力量 第7季第21集]
（关键在解读）
不太好吧
I don't know.
我想当人群转过这个角后
I think the line might panic when they turn this corner,
看见刀朝他们飞来会慌乱的
see the blade assembly up ahead.
（迪克来电）
挺奇怪的吧
Strange, isn't it,
居然有人起名叫迪克（混蛋）
someone would choose to be named Dick.
什么事
Yes?
这是凯文·谭的语音信箱
This is Kevin Tran's voicemail.
请留言
Please leave a message.
凯文 是妈妈
Kevin, it's mom.
我知道你已经在学校了
I know you're at school already,
马上要考试
about to take the test.
我知道你所有的辛苦努力
And I know all your hard work.
- 都将铸就你的成功 - 22了
- will net the results we've discussed… - 22!
- 搞毛啊 - 但就像恩德博士说的
- What?! - …but like Dr. Ender said,
别过分执着于「完美」
don't obsess on the "perfect."
不是吧 不是吧
No. No. No!
如果能成功 那就是锦上添花
That's just a nice feather in our cap, if we get it.
凯文 我们最后一节的研讨会马上结束了
Now, Kevin, we're about to finish up our last seminar.
我的飞机是早上七点的
My flight's confirmed for 7:00,
咱们明天早饭时见
So I'll see you at breakfast tomorrow.
我爱你 亲爱的
Love you, honey.
这场横贯大陆的暴风雨令人不解
…at a lost to explain the continent-wide storm system…
这暴风雨突如其来
that appeared seemingly out of nowhere,
电闪雷鸣笼罩了国家大部分地区
blanketing a good part of the nation in freak lightning displays.
马龙博士 美国气象学会的理事
Here with Dr. Marlon, price of the US meteorological society servey.
今天早些时候举行了一场新闻发布会
had a press conference earlier today.
我没有觉得「不解」
"Baffled"? No, I'm not baffled.
说实话 我觉得生气
Frankly, I'm offended.
这种天气现象实在反常
This is not the way weather behaves.
鲍比
Bobby?
鲍比 是你吗
Bobby, that you?
我想是的
Think so.
在罗曼那儿闹的那一出
But that whole adventure at Roman's.
似乎让他耗尽了能量
seems to have drained his batteries.
怎么回事
So, what?
这场到处在报道的风暴是我们整出来的吗
We start the storm heard 'round the world?
我们昨晚把这东西弄出来时
When we broke this thing open last night,
一百英里半径内的每个产房都人满为患
every maternity ward within a hundred-mile radius got slammed.
似乎所有在孕期最后一个月的孕妇
Looks like any woman in the last month of her pregnancy.
都生产了
went into labor.
这东西能影响女人啊
This one goes out to all the ladies.
这些重要的标示 预兆 查到什么了吗
So, heavyweight signs, omens … what do we got?
我想这是某种文字
I assume it's writing.
我从没见过这样的东西
I've never seen anything like it, ever.
而且在书上和网上也什么都没查到
And it doesn't match anything in any book or online.
好吧 超级大嘴怪降临人世
All right, so big daddy chomper lands here.
他弄了个叫迪克的皮囊
He grabs himself some Dick…
然后他开始秘密认购大学的各个系
and then he starts secretly underwriting university departments,
大量投资考古挖掘 都是为了找这个
pouring money into digs … all for this.
为什么呢
Why?
完全不知道
No clue.
但可以肯定不把这个弄回去
We do know that he will be tearing new ones.
他不会罢休
until he gets it back, though.
我们得稍微缓一缓
Look, we got to take a minute,
找个安全的地方 查明这东西的来头
hole up somewhere safe, find out what we've got.
去鲁弗斯的小屋怎么样
Rufus' cabin, then?
好
Yeah.
这次我去采购
This time, I'm doing the shopping.
梅格打来的
It's Meg.
怎么了
What?
你好啊 小帅哥
What up, Bullwinkle?
打电话给你们汇报一声 你们的好小伙醒了
Just a little FYI call. Your boy's awake.
什么 小卡醒了
What? Cass is awake.
什么时候 什么时候
When? When?
昨晚八点左右
Last night about 8:00.
你等到现在才告诉我们啊
And you waited till now to call us?
我忙着照顾小卡呢
I've been busy with Cass.
他和他昏迷的时候不太一样 知道吧
He's just a tad different than when he dozed off, 'kay?
你什么意思 什么不一样了
What do you mean, different?
大帅哥 你猜咋的 姐不是护士
Hey, Seacrest, guess what … not a nurse,
就在电视上扮过
just playing one on TV.
想要答案吗 开车过来吧
Want answers? Start driving.
好极了
Great.
去印第安纳州吗
So, Indiana?
是啊
Yeah.
昨晚八点
8:00 last night.
对
Yeah.
就是我们把那东西取出来的时间
Same time we opened up that thing.
哪位
Who?
凯文 你去哪儿了 考试都没参加
Kevin? Where were you today? You missed the test!
我…
I…
还有学生会和四重奏也没来
And student council and quartet.
我去取我妈妈的车了
I had to take my mom's car.
我好像发癫痫了
I think I had a seizure or something.
我是天选之子 天命如此
I've been chosen. It's my birthright.
天啊 凯文 你的压力太大了
Oh, my god, Kevin, all the pressure you've been under.
你不会也成了那种精神崩溃的神童吧
This isn't one of those overachiever-teen meltdowns, is it?
我得继续走
I'm supposed to keep going.
我不能停下来
I'm not allowed to stop.
什么叫不能
What do you mean, "Not allowed"?
你旁边有人吗
Is someone with you?
是他们逼你开走你妈妈的车吗
They didn't make you take your mother's car, did they?
凯文
Kevin?!
我们一路紧赶慢赶 这会儿我却没底气了
We raced all the way here. Now I don't know.
我真不敢面对残破不堪的他
I can't say I'm fired up to see what's left of the guy.
你觉得他什么都不记得了
You think he remembers at all?
是啊 而且我猜
That, and I'm guessing.
他从你那儿拿走的地狱梦魇
whatever kind of hell baggage he lifted off of your plate.
肯定是不容乐观
It's not gonna be pretty.
不好意思 两位 探访时间早过了
Hey. Excuse me, gentlemen, but it's way past visiting hours.
没事 艾伯 我等着他们呢
It's okay, Abel. I've been expecting them.
两位帅哥好
Hello, boys.
你好 小卡
Hey, Cass.
你好 迪恩
Hello, Dean.
萨姆
Sam.
你好 卡西迪奥
Hey, Castiel.
瞧瞧你 能说能走
Look at you, walkin' and talkin'.
真是太棒了 对吧
That's … that's great, right?
拉我的手指
Pull my finger.
干嘛
What?
我的手指
My finger …
拉一拉
Pull it.
等等 小卡
Just hang on, Cass. Wait.
我们先搞清楚你的状况
Let us catch up to you for a second.
你的意思是 你记得你是谁 你的身份
So, you're saying you remember who you are, what you are.
当然了
Yes. Of course.
今天在外面的花园里 我跟着一只蜜蜂
Outside today, in the garden, I followed a honeybee.
看到了采花的路线
I saw the route of flowers.
整个流程就摆在那儿
It's all right there, the whole plan.
不需要任何其他的东西
There's nothing to add.
你或许需要点安定
You might want to add a little thorazine.
对吧
Right?
他醒来之后就像个胡言乱语的裸奔男
He's been like the naked guy at the rave ever since he woke up.
彻头彻尾的废物
Totally useless.
你们瞧瞧她 我的看管人
Will you look at her? My caretaker.
那种刺疼的感觉 多么美啊
All of that thorny pain. So beautiful.
我们谈过的 我不喜欢吟诗作对
We've been over this. I don't like poetry.
给我闭嘴
Put up or shut up.
好吧
Okay.
小卡 你说你是昨晚醒来的对吧
So, Cass, you said you woke up last night?
对
Yes.
我听到了一个清脆的声音
I heard a ping that pierced me, and, well,
如果不是天使
you wouldn't have heard it.
你肯定听不到的
unless you were an angel at the time.
当时我们打开了这个
That's also when we opened this.
这样啊 我明白了
Oh. Of course. Now I understand.
明白什么了
Understand what?
就是你们啊
You're the ones.
好吧
Well…
这也说得通
…I guess that makes sense.
什么说得通
What makes sense?
如果说有谁能从地宫
If someone was going to free the word.
掘出神之语 那肯定就是你们两位了
from the vault of the earth, it would end up being you two.
我爱你们俩
I love you guys.
好了 差不多行了
Okay. All right. Okay.
行了
Yeah, yeah.
你先前说什么神之语
You said something about "The word."
是指写在上面的字吗
Is that what's written on there?
你们知道猫的阴茎上有锋利的倒刺吗
Did you know that a cat's penis is sharply barbed along its shaft?
我知道这种事不能跟女人讲
I know for a fact the females were not consulted about that.
小卡 我们形势很不利 知道吗
Cass, please, we're losing ground out there, okay?
我们需要你的帮助
We need your help.
你明白吗
Can you not see that?
这是梅塔特隆的笔迹
This is the handwriting of Metatron.
梅塔特隆
Metatron?
你说那玩意儿是变形金刚写的
You saying a transformer wrote that?
不 那是威震天
No. That's Megatron.
啥
What?!
变形金刚 是威震天
The transformer … it's Megatron.
啥
What?
梅塔特隆
Metatron.
他是天使
He's an angel.
神的书记员
He's the scribe of god.
创世的过程中 由他记录神的口谕
He took down dictation when creation was being formed.
那就是神之语了
And that's the word of god?
其中之一 没错
One of them, yes.
那到底写的是什么呢
Uh…well, what's it say, then?
树
"Tree"?
马 招潮蟹 我读不懂
"Horse"? "Fiddler crab"? I can't read it.
不是写给天使看的
It wasn't meant for angels.
好吧 真是糟透了
Okay, this all sounds bad.
你俩蠢货怎么会拿到神之语的
What are you two jackasses doing with the word of god?
让我看看
Let me see that thing.
退后 梅格
Back off, Meg.
拜托 这也是我的事
Come on, it's my ass, too.
退后
Back off.
妈的
Damn it!
这套「恶魔是二等公民」的架势滚一边去
Enough of this "Demons are second-class citizens" Crap!
不喜欢吵架
Don't like conflict.
怎么回事
What the hell was that?
你听到了 他说不喜欢吵架
You heard him. He doesn't like conflict.
他去休息室了 我能担保
He's down in the dayroom now. I guarantee it.
好吧 我去搞定小卡
All right, I'll go handle Cass.
萨姆 你能负责收拾神之语吗
Sam, will you please pick up the word of god?
好
Yeah.
你们这是惹了什么麻烦
What are you guys caught up in now?
我有权知道 萨姆
I deserve to know, Sam.
好吧
Okay, fine.
那我走了
I'll hit the road, then.
我带上我的天使就上路了
Let me just go get my angel.
梅格 你说什么呢 站住
Meg, what are you talking about? Stop.
我们一起喊 你说小卡会跟谁走
We both call, who do you think Cass will come to?
应该是我吧
I'm guessing me.
你也听到了 什么带刺的美人儿
You heard him … thorny beauty, blah, blah.
我是陪在他身边的圣徒
I'm the saint who stayed with him.
他欠我的 他的原话
He owes me. His words.
那他欠我们的怎么算
Yeah, what about what he owes us?
对他施展魅力吧
Well, work on him a little.
没准他会爱上你呢 帅哥
Maybe he'll start crushing on you, too, hot stuff.
神经兮兮的天使对你有什么用 别傻了
What are you gonna do with a broken angel? Don't be stupid.
我对获取力量不挑拣
I'll take power where I can get it.
我还要照顾我自己呢
I've got myself to look out for.
怎么回事
What the hell?
别追了 别来追我
No, stop, leave me alone.
不是恶魔也不是大嘴怪 你到底是什么
Not a demon or a chomper. What the hell are you?
我是凯文·谭
I'm a… K-Kevin Tran.
我在读大学预修课 不要杀我
I'm in advanced placement. P-p-p-p-please don't kill me.
我没打算杀你
I'm not gonna kill you.
对不起
I'm sorry.
对不起 我…
I-I'm sorry. I…
我不知道怎么回事 但我不能放手
I don't … I don't know why, but I can't let go of this.
知道你打碎了神之语吗
You realize you just broke god's word?
是萨姆的那些噩梦对吗
It's Sam's thing, isn't it?
你把他的创伤后遗症弄到自己身上了
You taking on his, uh, cage-match scars.
这就是你现在变成这样的原因 对吧
I'm guessing that's what broke your bank, right?
我走到这一步 费尽千辛万苦
Well, it took… everything to get me here.
你在说什么呢 老兄
What are you talking about, man?
迪恩 我知道你不想听这个
Dean, I know you want different answers.
不 我想你扣上风衣
No, I want you to button up your coat.
帮助我们搞定利维坦
and help us take down Leviathans.
你还记得你做过什么吗
Do you remember what you did?
（抱歉）
你要先走吗
Do you want to go first?
你还真蹚进这趟浑水了 孩子
You really stepped in it, kid.
真可怜
Oh, man.
我只知道这 这是我的
All I know is, this is … it's for me.
这应该由我保管
I'm supposed to keep it.
祝你好运
Good luck.
但你也不知道那是什么
But you don't know what it is?
打开
Open it.
开始谁也不知道
You know, we weren't sure at first.
哪种猴子能活下来
which monkeys were gonna make it.
别生气 不过我当时喜欢尼安德塔人（穴居人）
No offense, but I was backing the Neanderthals.
他们的诗实在太美了
because their poetry was…just amazing.
与周围环境浑然一体
It's in perfect tune with the spheres.
但最终 还是你们
But in the end, it was you …
你们这些现代智人的后人
The home sapiens sapiens.
你们这些家伙偷吃了苹果 创造了裤子
You guys ate the apple, invented pants.
小卡 我们去哪儿找这个梅塔特隆
cass, where do we find this, uh, Metatron?
他还活着吗
Is he still alive?
抱歉 不过你得退回原点
I'm sorry. I … I think you have to go back to start.
这事真的很重要
This is important.
我觉得梅塔特隆能够阻止很多坏事
I think Metatron could stop a lot of bad.
你明白吗
You understand that?
我们住在一个很「抱歉」的星球
We live in a "Sorry" universe.
这里就该充满冲突
It's engineered to create conflict.
比如 我为何能从你的不幸中
I mean, why should I prosper from…
获利呢
your misfortune?
但规矩就是规矩
But these are the rules.
规矩不是我定的
I didn't make them.
有些就是你定的
You made some of them.
当你试图变成上帝
When you tried to become God,
打开墙上的那个洞时
when you cut that hole through that wall.
迪恩
Dean…
该你了
…it's your move.
别下了
Forget the damn game!
别玩游戏了 小卡
Forget the game, cass.
我很抱歉 迪恩
I'm sorry, Dean.
不
No.
「抱歉」只是一盘棋
You're playing "Sorry"
上头都是字
It's writing.
是的 是的 我们知道
Yeah. Yeah, we get that.
利维坦是什么
What's Leviathan?
什么 你能认出来 上头写着吗
What? You can read it? Is that what it says?
差不多吧 很费劲
Sort of. It hurts a little.
我就像戴着别人的眼镜在看这些字
Like looking through somebody else's glasses,
但我觉得这个
but I think it…
上面写着关于利维坦的事 他们的出处
It's about Leviathan, how it came to be.
上帝把他锁进了深渊 对吧
God locked him up far away, right?
就像关进了监狱 因为他们非常
Like in jail… because they're so…
他们
They're…
他们真实存在的 对吗
…they're real, aren't they?
对 凯文 他们存在 在地球上
Yeah, Kevin. They … they are. And they're here.
有写怎么杀死他们吗
Does it say anything about how to kill them?
因为 他们很难杀死
'cause that's … that's kind of been a problem.
不知道 这不像普通的阅读
I don't know. It's not like reading reading.
很难长时间集中注意力
It … it's hard to focus on it too long.
萨姆 出事了
Sam. Something's up.
什么
What?
凯文 淡定
Kevin, hey, hey, hey.
凯文
Kevin.
恶魔
Demon.
怎么了
What?
是萨姆
Sam.
他在跟天使说话
He's talking to angels.
恶魔婊子和温家兄弟 又是这种组合
A demon whore and a Winchester…again.
离先知远点
Step away from the prophet!
你说谁 我
Who, me?
凡间唯一的神之语的守护者 我们来带你走
Sole keeper of the word on earth, we are here to take you.
你说「带我走」是什么意思
What do you mean, "Take"?
杀了这个恶魔和她的小情人
Kill the demon and her lover.
不是这样的 我们不是
That's not how it … we're not …
你从哪里搞来的
Where did you get that?!
卡西迪奥
Castiel?
你还活着
You're alive?
你这家伙
You.
你好 海斯特
Hello, Hester.
你在天堂大开杀戒
You smote thousands in heaven.
说了番恐怖的话 然后就消失了
You gave a big, scary speech. Then you were gone.
那算怎么回事
What the hell was that?!
首先 那确实不太礼貌
Rude, for one thing.
你去哪儿了
Where have you been?
埃纳亚斯
Oh, Inias.
海斯特 我
Hester, I…
我知道你在找什么
I know you want something …
解决之道
Answers.
我
I…
我真希望我能帮你们
I wish it could be that …
但我还能教你很多东西
There are still many things I can teach you.
我能开拓你们的视角
I can offer, um, well, perspective.
来
Here.
拉我的手指
Pull my finger.
梅格会去换盏灯
Meg will … will get another light,
我来把它灭了
and I'll … I'll blow it out again.
这样会很有趣
And, well, this time, it'll be funny,
我们回想过去 笑笑就过去了
and we'll all look back and laugh.
你疯了吧
You're insane.
小心点 小美女
Heads up, sunshine.
所有的天使都滚回老家了
All angels blown back to their corners.
我们最多有三四个小时
We got like three, four hours tops.
梅格 你从哪儿弄来的
Meg, where did you get that?
今年死了很多天使
A lot of angels died this year.
怎么回事啊
What's happening?!
这是谁
What is that?
他叫凯文·谭
It's, uh… Kevin Tran.
他是预科生
He's, uh, in advanced placement.
这么说这些利维坦 这些怪物是真的
So, these Leviathans … these monsters are real.
那带翼天使呢
And angels with wings?
不
No. Uh…
没有翅膀 什么都没有
No wings. No anything.
啥乱七八糟的都没有
No junk. Junkless.
凯文 你能认出上帝之石上的那些鬼画桃符
So, Kevin, you can, uh, read the chicken scratch on the God rock?
又变成一整块了
That is back in one piece, I see.
你说那上面写着
And you're saying that there's some sort of.
「杀死迪克指南」吗
a "How to punch Dick" recipe in there somewhere?
我不明白你的意思
I don't know what you're saying,
但我觉得这就像是紧急情况指南
But it seems kind of like an "In case of emergency" Note.
他们为什么喊我先知
What did they mean by "Prophet"?
不是吧 来真的
Oh, no. Really?
是 天使是这么说的
Yeah. Yeah, that's what the angel said.
我才不想做什么先知
I don't want to be a prophet.
对 谁也不想
No. You don't at all.
先生们 咱们得开始逃了
Gentlemen, we've got to start running and hiding.
除非你们想留下继续跟他们纠缠
Or do you want to tangle with those wing nuts twice?
对不起 谁跟你「咱们」
I'm sorry. Did you say "We"?
我现在被天使们盯上了
I'm on the angels' radar now.
我得多拉些人保全性命
You think I don't need a little safety in numbers?
好吧 咱们回鲁弗斯的小屋
All right, we'll go to Rufus' cabin.
让这孩子去那儿做读书报告
Kid can do his book report there.
您饿了吧
We know you're hungry.
来比格森自制馅饼吧饱餐一顿呢
Why not enjoy Biggerson's homemade pie bar?
卖馅饼的沙拉吧
It's like a salad bar but with pie.
继续播报新闻十台的头条新闻
Now back to our top story on News 10,
失踪好学生一案的搜寻进展
the search for the missing honor student.
此案的受害人
The victim in this case.
据称坚持他天命如此
reportedly insisted he'd been chosen by birthright,
使人们猜测绑架可能与邪教有关
causing speculation that a cult may be behind the abduction.
家里的车也一同丢失
The family car is also missing.
联邦政府已经处于戒备状态
Federal authorities have been placed on alert.
再次报道 十六岁的好学生凯文·谭
Again, 16-year-old honor student Kevin Tran.
昨日早些时候被人从他密歇根的家中带走
reportedly taken from his Michigan home early yesterday.
糟糕
Oh, crap.
一波未平一波又起
So, we got another wrinkle.
貌似凯文据报失踪了
Uh, looks like Kevin's gone missing…
而联邦政府正在调查
And it's gone federal.
就这么背
Yeah.
梅格呢
Where's Meg?
我在这呢
I'm here.
真好 现在我们成绑架犯了
Great, so now we're kidnappers?
别乱说不就得了
Not if we shut up about it.
怎么了 我们绑架了谁
Why? Who'd we kidnap?
天哪
Oh, God.
怎么了
What?
没事
Nothing. Nothing.
就是
Just…
我的生活
My life…
我的未来
My future…
我的女朋友
My girlfriend…
我妈的车
My mom's car.
卡西迪奥 是我
Yeah, Castiel. It's me.
小卡 在哪 他在哪
Cass? Where? Where is he?
闭嘴 不 小卡 你说
Shut up. No. No, Cass. You talk.
- 珀斯 - 澳大利亚的那个「珀斯」吗
- Perth? - "Perth"? As in Australia?
什么狗
What dogs?
他说他被一群愤怒的狗狗包围了
He says he's surrounded by unhappy dogs.
好的
Oh. Okay.
他在珀斯的赛狗赛道上
He's at a dog track in Perth.
我被一群愤怒的大狗包围了
I'm surrounded by large unhappy dogs.
它们愤怒是因为兔子是假的
Yeah, they're unhappy 'cause the rabbit's fake.
我们在明尼苏达州圣克芬德北面的94号公路
Listen, we're on Highway 94, north of St. Cloud, Minnesota,
刚经过79英里标志牌
Just passing mile marker 79.
凯文 这位是卡西迪奥
Kevin, this is Castiel.
你也是个天使
You're one of the angels?
- 梅格 你受伤了吗 - 闭嘴
- Meg, are you hurt? - Shut up.
伙计们 刚刚怎么回事 那些人是谁
Guys, what happened back there? Who were those guys?
他们是卫戍队的人 以前是我的卫戍队
They're from the garrison… my old garrison.
看来海斯特接管了
Looks like Hester's taken over.
我们的任务是守望地球
We were assigned to watch the earth.
通常都很无聊
Often, it was boring.
战争很无聊 还有性爱
The wars were very boring and the sex…
都是一样的套路
You know, the repetition.
总之 我
Anyway, I was, uh…
我是他们的队长
I was their captain.
是不是很奇怪
Isn't that strange?
小卡 他们干嘛现在来找我们麻烦
Cass, why are they pissed at us now?
那些赛狗真是惨啊
You know, those racing dogs were absolutely miserable.
他们的思维都是赛道型的
They can only think in ovals.
小卡 别逼我靠边停车
Cass, don't make me pull this car over!
天使为什么追着我们
Why are angels after us?
你生气了吗 你为什么要生气
Are you angry? Why are you angry?
没有 我
No, I-I'm…
拜托 能不能说正事
Please, can we just stay on target?
没必要生气 他们只是照章办事
There is no reason for anger. They're only following protocol.
当神之语显现
If the word of God is revealed,
其守护者就会苏醒
a keeper of the word will awaken,
就像这个烫手山芋
like this hot potato right here.
别这样
Please stop that.
总之
Anyway,
卫戍队法令指示其队员带守护者去沙漠
garrison code dictates you take the keeper to the desert.
远离人类 而后得悉神之语
to learn the word away from men.
这是什么道理
What kind of sense does that make?
他得告诉我们讲了什么 我们才好加以利用
He has to tell us so that we can use it.
这就是上帝的鬼把戏
That's God and his shiny red apples.
我不能住在沙漠里 我在申请普林斯顿大学
I can't live in the desert. I-I'm applying to Princeton!
我和你说 去他妈的卫戍队
Okay, you know what? Screw the garrison.
我们需要那块碑
We need the tablet.
来终结迪克·罗曼的吃死我们的阴谋
to end Dick Roman's "soylent us" crap.
如果你要知道神之语
If you want the word,
就得躲着海斯特和她手下
you'll have to duck Hester and her soldiers.
你和我们是一条战线的吧 小卡
Yeah, you're in our corner, right, Cass?
我不会再战斗了
No, I don't fight anymore.
我观察蜜蜂
I watch the bees.
别画天使驱逐符了 我也会被你们驱逐的
Let's leave off angel-proofing sigils or I'll be expelled, too.
只要你的卫戍队员看不到我们
As long as we're invisible to your garrison buddies,
我无所谓
it works for me.
你肯定很饿了
I'm sure you're pretty hungry,
楼上的事一搞定
so once we get settled in upstairs,
我们就弄点晚餐
we'll get some dinner going.
这里看起来像是性虐地牢
This looks like a sex-torture dungeon.
这里是性虐地牢吗
Is this a sex-torture dungeon?
不 这里不是性虐
No, this is not a sex-torture…
过来 坐下看碑
Get over here. Sit down and read, would you?
你似乎有心事
You seem troubled.
不过你这人就是这样
Of course, that's a primary aspect of your personality,
所以我有时不去管你
so I sometimes ignore it.
好吧
Okay. Um…
我现在是在想你的事
…right now I'm just wondering about you.
我什么事
What about me?
你在担心我从你身上接过的重担
You're worried about the burden I lifted from you.
我以为我完了
I think I was done for.
你能看到路西法吗
Do you see Lucifer?
一开始看到了
I did at first.
那是
It was…
像是你梦魇的投射 类似余味
It was a projection of yours, I think, sort of an aftertaste.
而现在我看到的更多是
Now I more see…
天地万物
well, everything.
很好笑 我本来也完了
It's funny. I was… I was done for, too.
我造的孽的重责
The weight of all my mistakes,
那些失去的生命和灵魂
all those lives and souls lost, I…
我也无法承受
I couldn't take it, either.
我
I was…
我本迷失方向 直到接过你的痛苦
I was lost until I took on your pain.
说起来奇怪 这反而会帮了我
It's strange to think that that helped, but…
我知道你一心想帮忙
I know you never did anything but try to help.
我知道 小卡 我也很感激
I realize that, Cass, and I'm grateful.
我们都很感激
We're all grateful.
我们会帮你好转起来的
And we're gonna help you get better, okay?
不计一切代价
No matter what it takes.
什么叫「好转起来」
What do you mean, "better"?
凯文
Kevin.
我受不了了
This is all too much.
我的生活怎么了
What's happened to my life?
我只是个密歇根的孩子
I'm just a kid from Michigan.
我不想做神之语的守护者
I didn't want to be a word keeper!
看来得用呼吸袋了
Looks like we're brown-baggin' it.
我还没准备好接受世界上存在超自然力量呢
I am not prepared to factor the supernatural into my world view.
好了 就这样
Okay, there we go.
就这样 吸气呼气 放松
That's it. That's it. Just breathe. Take it easy.
我也不知道该说什么
I don't know, man. What can I say?
你是天选之子
You've been chosen.
这感觉糟透了 相信我
And it sucks. Believe me.
问「为什么选我」是没用的
There's no use asking "Why me?"
因为天使根本不在乎
'cause the angels… they don't care.
也许他们就是关心无能
I think maybe they just don't have the equipment to care.
看来他们想去关心的时候
Seems like when they try, it just…
就会崩溃
…breaks them apart.
我只是想成为第一个
I just want to be the first Asian-American.
亚裔美国总统
president of the united states.
先干活吧
Then do your homework.
我如约而至了
See? I'm here, just like I said.
最好说点有用的 荡妇
You'd better start talking, skank.
你说我干嘛不拖着你
Tell me again why I'm not just hauling you off.
去找地狱之王领赏
to the king's cash window.
别这样 拉斯科
Come on, Rosco.
我说了 我手上有更好的东西
I told you. I've got something way better.
你们知道克劳力喜欢礼物
You know how Crowley likes presents.
他才不在乎温家兄弟呢
He's not gonna care if we bring in the Winchesters.
都好久的事了
Yesterday's news.
不是温彻斯特兄弟
Not the Winchesters.
我有出卖他的那个天使
I've got the angel who double-crossed him.
我找到了卡西迪奥
I've got Castiel.
卡西迪奥 他已经死了
Castiel … he's dead.
是啊 你什么都知道
Right, 'cause you're in that loop.
那他在哪儿
Where is he, then?
首先 我要知道我得跟你们多少人分赏钱
First, I want to know how many of you jerks I have to cut in.
你以为我们傻吗
You think we're stupid?
我们可没有告诉别人
We didn't tell anybody.
我爱死恶魔了
I love demons.
没想到你还回来了
Didn't expect to see you back.
对 没有跟恶魔军团一起回来
Yeah, not without the King's army.
刀
Knife.
总是这样
Typical.
我救了所有人
I save our bacon,
而你们画个恶魔陷阱在这儿等我
and you're sitting here, waiting by a devil's trap.
说真的 我刚刚杀了两个克劳力的手下
Seriously, I just killed two of Crowley's men.
我本可出卖你们
I could have gone the other way on that.
这是真的
It's true, incidentally.
刀上还有其他恶魔的血
There's other demons' blood on that blade.
我比你们想的要单纯得多
Look, I'm simpler than you think.
我悟出了这世间的一个道理
I've figured one thing out about this world …
就那么一个
Just one, pretty much.
找到一个目标 然后为之效力
You find a cause, and you serve it.
沉溺于此 碌碌一生
Give yourself over, and it orders your life.
而我就是为了拯救路西法和黄眼怪
Lucifer and yellow eyes … their mission was it for me.
那我们就该相信你
So, what? We should trust you.
因为你要解救地狱里的撒旦
because you wanted to free satan from hell?
我说的是目标 傻逼
I'm talking "Cause, " douche bag,
就像早上起床的理由
As in reason to get up in the morning.
很显然 此一时彼一时
Obviously, these things shift over time.
我们长教训 变成熟
We learn, we grow.
而现在我的目标就是击败地狱之王
Now, for me currently, the cause is bringing down the King.
我也知道我需要帮手
And I know we'll need help to do it.
克劳力现在可不是什么麻烦
Crowley ain't the problem this year.
你什么时候能明白 克劳力永远是麻烦
When are you gonna get it? Crowley's always the problem.
他只是在等合适的时机出手
He's just waiting for the right moment to strike.
我知道我该干嘛
I know what I'm supposed to do.
这不会伤害萨姆和迪恩
And it isn't screw with Sam and Dean.
或是唯一会挺我的天使
Or lose the only angel who'd go to bat for me.
很好
This is good …
和谐共处 相互沟通
Harmony, communication.
现在我们唯一的麻烦就是海斯特
Now our only problem is Hester.
什么
What?
我们在躲避卫戍队的追捕
Well, here, we're hidden from the garrison,
但你杀了个恶魔 我们就彻底暴露了
But when you killed a demon, you put out a pretty clear beacon.
我们得马上增强天使驱逐符
We need better angel-proofing now.
你居然从我们手中夺走先知
You took the prophet from us?!
对不起
I'm … I'm sorry?
你已经彻头彻尾的堕落了
You have fallen in every way imaginable.
求你 卡西迪奥
Please, Castiel.
我们必须遵循法令 帮我们完成工作吧
We have to follow the code. Help us do our work.
他不能帮助你 他谁也帮不了
He can't help you. He can't help anybody.
我们不需要他的帮助
We don't need his help…
或是应允
Or his permission.
今晚就带守护者去沙漠
The keeper goes to the desert tonight.
你们别多事
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Back off.
我们可是在帮你们天使擦屁股
We're actually trying to clean up one of your angel's messes!
你知道的
You know that.
他说的没错
He's right.
是某个天使把利维坦带回了这个世界
An angel brought the leviathan back into this world,
当时他们恳求他
and … and they begged him.
求他不要这么做
They begged him not to do it.
给我们点时间好吗
Look, just give us some time, okay?
我们会照看好先知的
We will take care of your prophet.
为什么我们还要给你任何东西
Why should we give you anything…
你拿走的还不够多吗
After everything you have taken from us?
你毁灭了一切
The very touch of you corrupts.
当初卡西迪奥从地狱救你出来 他就迷失了
When Castiel first laid a hand on you in hell, he was lost!
为此 你就要付出代价
For that, you're going to pay.
别这样
Please.
我们来这儿是为了保护他们的
They're the ones we were put here to protect.
不 卡西迪奥
No, Castiel.
该停止疯狂了
No more madness!
该停止许诺了
No more promises!
去你的新上帝
No more new gods!
海斯特 住手
Hester! No!
求你了
Please!
天使已经所剩无几了
There's so few of us left.
你想要自由意志
You wanted free will.
现在我说了算
Now I'm making the choices.
怎么了
What?
总得有人下手吧
Someone had to.
奇怪的年月啊
These are strange times.
我觉得就没正常过
I think they've always been.
真希望你能跟我们来
I wish you'd come with us.
我不再是卫戍队的一员了 埃纳亚斯
Oh, I'm not part of the garrison anymore, Inias.
对不起
I'm sorry.
谢谢你 凯文
Thanks, Kevin.
很多人会承受不来
Not a lot of people could handle this.
你都写完了吗 天选之子
You doing all right there, "Chosen one"?
是的
Yeah.
你准备好了吗 凯文·谭
Are you ready, Kevin Tran?
送守护者回家 我们可以在那儿照看他
Bring the keeper to his home. We can watch over him there.
我找不到梅格了
I couldn't find Meg anywhere.
她比较喜欢躲起来
Yes, well, she enjoys laying low.
看这儿
Here.
若要杀死利维坦
Leviathan cannot be slain.
只能用正直凡人之骨
but by a bone of a righteous mortal.
浸以三滴堕落天使之血
washed in the three bloods of the fallen.
上面说我们先要找到堕落天使的血
It says we need to start with the blood of a fallen angel.
你们了解我的
Well, you know me.
我总是愿意为温家兄弟流血
I'm always happy to bleed for the Winchesters.
你接下来要怎么办 小卡
What are you gonna do, Cass?
我不知道
I don't know.
这多好
Isn't that amazing?
我们去干活吧
Well, let's get to work.
我们已经尽力了
We're doing everything we can.
谭女士 相信我
Mrs. Tran, believe me.
他说他发了癫痫
He said he'd had a s-seizure.
要是他们打他了呢
What … what if they hit him?
要是他脑损伤了呢
What if he has a brain injury?
你要相信我们 好吗
You need to trust us, okay?
你瞎担心也是没有用的
It won't help to wear yourself out with worry.
妈妈
Mom?
凯文
Kevin!
你们是谁
Who are you?
没事的 妈妈 是他们带我回来的
It's … it's okay, mom. They brought me back.
我们是来保护我的
They're keeping me safe.
恐怕不是这样的
I don't believe that's true.
石头打败剪刀
Rock beats scissor.
利维坦杀死天使
Leviathan beats angel.
你好 凯文
Hello, Kevin.